<resources>
    <string name="app_name">codesgtasanandreas</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="waepon"> LXGIWYL - set of weapons №1 for amateurs (brass knuckles, Baseball Bat, 9mm pistol, shotgun, micro SMG, AK-47, rifle, rocket launcher, Molotov cocktail, spraycan).\n\nPROFESSIONALSKIT, KJKSZPJ - set of weapons №2 for professionals (knife, pistol Desert Eagle, shotgun Sawn-off, Tec-9, M4, sniper rifle, fire extinguisher, flamethrower, grenades).\n\nUZUMYMW - set of weapons №3 for the crazies (chainsaw, a silenced pistol, combat shotgun, MP5, M4, Heat Seeking Rocket Launcher, bomb with remote control).\n\n
FULLCLIP WANRLTW - infinite amount of ammo and shooting without reloading.\n\n
NCSGDAG PROFESSIONALKILLER - the highest level of knowledge of all kinds of weapons\n\n
OUIQDMW - automatic focus when shooting from machine</string>
    <string name="weather">AFZLLQLL - the Sunny weather\n\n
ICIKPYH - the weather is very sunny\n\n
ALNSFMZO - cloud weather\n\n
AUIFRVQS - rainy weather\n\n
CFVFGMJ - the foggy weather\n\n
MGHXYRM - storm\n\n
CWJXUOC - Buran (sandstorm)\n\n YSOHNUL - accelerate playing time\n\n
PPGWJHT - speed up the game (gameplay)\n\n
LIYOAAY - slow gameplay\n\n
XJVSNAJ NIGHTPROWLER - always midnight. The game clock is stopped at 00:00. If you die, it will return noon - 12:00.</string>
    <string name="other"> HESOYAM - full health, armor and $250,000\n\n
BAGUVIX - infinite health protection from bullets, fire and shock, however you still can suffer from the explosions, falling from a height, collision of a car  or drown\n\n
CVWKXAM - unlimited breath under water\n\n
AEDUWNV - always hungry, never to be hungry\n\n
MUNASEF ANOSEONGLASS - adrenaline level\n\nASNAEB TURNDOWNTHEHEAT - remove wanted level (all the stars disappear).\n\n
LJSPQK BRINGITON - increase wanted level to the maximum (6 star search).\n\n
OSRBLHH TURNUPTHEHEAT - increase wanted level by 2 stars\n\n
AEZAKMI - elusive, never get caught and arrested\n\nOGXSDAG WORSHIPME - maximum respect\n\n
EHIBXQS HELLOLADIES - maximum attractiveness.\n\n
BTCDBCB - CJ is very thick\n\n
KVGYZQK - CJ is skinny\n\n
BUFFMEUP JYSDSOD - CJ is muscular hunk\n\n
VKYPQCF - Max Stamina\n\ngit init
VQIMAHA NATURALTALENT - CJ maximum level of driving all transport\n\n
BIFBUZZ - gang seized absolutely the entire state of San Andreas. The streets of cities are completely empty, no one except the bandits of opposite groups that are fighting without respite.\n\n
MROEMZH gangs everywhere, they will surround you everywhere, even where they shouldn't (for example, Ballases in Las Venturas).\n\nAJLOJYQY - People hit each other with golfclubs\n\n
BAGOWPG - Have a bounty on your head.\n\n
FOOOXFT - All armed.\n\n
SZCMAWO - Suicide.\n\n
ASBHGRB - Elvises everywhere.\n\n
BGLUAWML - People attack you with weapons.\n\n
CIKGCGX - Party on the beach.\n\n
MROEMZH - gang Members everywhere.\n\n
BIFBUZZ - Control of the streets.\n\n
AFPHULTL - Ninja.\n\n
BEKKNQV - Girl… .\n\n
JHJOECW - Huge Bunny Hop.\n\n
LFGMHAL - Mega jumps.\n\n
IAVENJQ - Mega hit.\n\n
AEDUWNV - You don't know the word "hunger".\n\n
IOJUFZN - Riot mode.\n\n
PRIEBJ - Funhouse Theme.\n\n
OUIQDMW - the Complete weapon aiming in the car.\n\n
THGLOJ - Abbreviation of the movement.\n\n
SJMAHPE - the Recruitment of any (9mm).\n\n
ZSOXFSQ - the Recruitment of any (Rockets).\n\n
CRAZYTOWN - everyone is crazies\n\n
NATURALTALENT - all your skills pumped to the maximum parameters.\n\n

    </string>
    <string name="cars">AIWPRTON - Rhino tank\n\n
CQZIJMB - Bloodring Banger\n\n
PDNEJOH - Hotring Racer 73\n\n
VPJTQWV - Hotring Racer 07\n\n
AQTBCODX - Romero\n\n
KRIJEBR - Stretch\n\n
UBHYZHQ - Trashmaster\n\n
RZHSUEW - golfcar Caddy\n\n
AKJJYGLC FOURWHEELFUN - Quadbike\n\n
AMOMHRER - Tanker Truck\n\n
EEGCYXT - Dozer\n\n
AGBDLCID - Monster\n\n
JQNTDMH - Rancher\n\nJUMPJET - plane Hydra\n\n
OHDUDE - helicopter Hunter\n\n
URKQSRK - Stunt Plane\n\nKGGGDKP - Vortex Hovercraft\n\n
ROCKETMAN YECGAA - Jetpack\n\n
AIYPWZQP - get the parachute\n\nCOXEFGU - all the cars have nitro, but its stock is limited so to meet the need to get out and sit back in the car.\n\n
CPKTNWT - explode all cars. All machines in the field of visibility of the player will shoot up into the air.\n\n
XICWMD - all transport becomes invisible (transparent), except motorcycles. Wheels are the only visible part of car.\n\n
PGGOMOY - perfect control. Increases the sensitivity and sharpness in the driving.\n\n
ZEIIVG - traffic lights are always green. Stable light is green.\n\n
YLTEICZ - aggressive drivers. Drivers and their passengers engage in a shootout with police.\n\n
LLQPFBN AGRUXVHIQYH - the color of all cars becomes pink. More glamour in San Andreas.\n\n
IOWDLAC AGRUJRYMNOL - the color of all machines is black. Mourning in the state…\n\n
RIPAZHA - flying cars. Speeding car can fly. control like in the plane.\n\n
FVTMNBZ - all cars and people from the countryside. Cities of the state of San Andreas go rednecks.\n\n
AFSNMSMW - flying boats. All boats and yachts fly, though boats could not fly high, because it's too heavy.\n\n
BGKGTJH - on the streets SA only cheap slower cars.\n\n
GUSNHDE - on the streets SA expensive fast and sports car.\n\n
BSXSGGC BUBBLECARS - the slightest collision of your machine with other car they lose weight and fly up.\n\n
JCNRUAD - any car that you sit in becomes practically not killable, and collisions with other transport breaks.\n\n
CVWKXAM - the result of the code is not defined.\n\n
VKYPQCF - the result of the code is not defined.\n\n
BMTPWHR - the result of the code is not defined.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3861995689830617/95934292741</string>
</resources>
